# James Washington

# Highly experienced fast paced worker

Brooklyn Park, MN 55443 datonawiccked@gmail.com 9189224997

Very customer savvy, highly trained cashier an customer service representative, enjoys high pace work environments, works very well within a team or alone, has warehouse an carpentry experience, some construction sanding, nailgun, concrete mixing "by hand", general labor an clean up.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

# **Machine Operator/Material Handler**

Diversified Plastics - Brooklyn Park, MN September 2020 to October 2020

Operation of multiple press machines, labeling an packaging plastic products

# **Dishwasher/Prep Cook**

The Summit Club of Tulsa - Tulsa, OK December 2017 to September 2020

• Wash dishes, an prep

### Warehouse Associate (Seasonal)

Party Pro Rents - Tulsa, OK September 2017 to January 2018

Collected an counted outgoing an incoming rented items or will call

- Picked, packed, and shipped items
- Made sure all items were clean
- Supervised shipping and receiving
- Inspected and crated merchandise
- Staged orders

### **Dishwasher**

Cracker barrel - Tulsa, OK January 2015 to December 2015

Responsibilities

Operate dishwasher, provide cooks with clean dishes, clean tables

Skills Used

Dishwasher operation

#### **McDonalds Crew Member**

McDonald's Corporate

#### 2013 to 2015

### Houseman

Doubletree by Hilton - Tulsa, OK September 2013 to April 2014

### Responsibilities

Load an unload laundry, vacuum multiple floors "all assigned" clean various parts of the building

# **Pallet Jack Operator**

Atlas Staffing, Inc. - Robbinsdale, MN October 2012 to October 2013

Operated pallet Jack, load an unload freight trucks

# **Cook/Cashier store opener**

TACO BUENO - Dell City, TX
December 2011 to September 2012

#### Responsibilities

Open store an all duties required; prep all fresh foods, set up salsa bar, cook beans, cook breakfast items, raw steak an chicken, work the line making burritos tacos an salads

#### Accomplishments

One month shift leader training

#### Skills Used

Cook/cashiering/customer service

#### **Education**

# High school or equivalent

North High School

# Skills

- Carpentry (1 year)
- Cashier (10+ years)
- Customer Service (10+ years)
- Stocking (1 year)
- · High school math skills
- Basic hand tools (3 years)
- Cash Handling (10+ years)
- Computers (2 years)
- Warehouse (2 years)
- Material handling (2 years)
- Pallet Jack (3 years)

- Food Prep
- Kitchen Staff
- Grill
- Food Service
- · Load & Unload
- Shipping & Receiving
- Cleaning Experience
- Time management

# Certifications and Licenses

### food handlers

### **Food Handler**

### Assessments

# **Customer Focus & Orientation — Expert**

September 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: Expert

# **Work Style: Reliability — Expert**

September 2020

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.

Full results: Expert

## **Work Motivation — Expert**

September 2020

Level of motivation and discipline applied toward work

Full results: Expert

# **Work Style: Reliability — Expert**

September 2020

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.

Full results: Expert

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.